WILL HOLDSWORTH

www.willholdsworth.com hello@willholdsworth.com 07903377729 Wixams, Bedfordshire, MK42 6FA

QUALITIES

Over 10 years of experience in global B2C, B2B, and B2B2C e-commerce design and marketing, including brand design and luxury industries.

Extensive skills as a marketing strategist and designer in 2D/3D design, typographic design, digital design, photography, videography, video editing, motion graphics, and UI/UX design.

Effective in leading projects independently and managing teams across multiple workstreams.

Comprehensive experience directing internal teams and external stakeholders to deliver effective campaign strategies.

Ensured consistency in company ethos, campaign strategies, and global brand messaging.

Creative problem solver with a quick learning curve for new skills.

SKILLS

- Digital Design & UI/UX Tools: Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Firefly AI), Adobe XD
- Video Production: Davinci Resolve, Adobe After Effects
- 3D Design and Animation: Blender
- Al Coding/Design Tools: Copilot, Gemini, Workik, Luminar Al, ElevenLabs, NotebookLM.
- Project Management & Communication: Microsoft Office Suite (Excel, Word, PowerPoint)
- Email Marketing/Analysis: Mailchimp
- Social Media Management/Analytics: Later.com

EDUCATION

ILLUSTRATION / GRAPHIC DESIGN

2:1 BA Hons

The University of Portsmouth

FOUNDATION DIPLOMA

Distinction (Art & Design)
Oaklands College St. Albans

A-LEVELS

Photography, Art, Psychology The Hemel Hempstead School

GSCES

Mathematics **B** English **BC** Science **BB** The Hemel Hempstead School

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SENIOR MARKETING DESIGNER

FUTURE SOUND & VISION LTD NOVEMBER 2017 – PRESENT (42.5)

Responsible for generating all visual content, guidelines, marketing strategies, and collateral for Future Sound & Vision and its subsidiaries (Future Automation, Matthew Hill Bespoke, Shading Pro).

- Led the comprehensive rebrand of Future Sound & Vision and its subsidiaries, aligning creative output with target markets and business objectives, contributing to a 24x revenue growth over 7 years.
- Secured contracts with high-profile clients such as Harrods, Apple, and Tottenham Hotspur by developing 3D design skills to generate high quality pitch documents.
- Created Al-driven solutions to automate artwork layouts and generate marketing materials, significantly reducing production time and increasing efficiency.
- Directed and executed numerous photo and video shoots for completed projects, producing high-quality visual content for marketing collateral and campaigns.
- Identified and managed key social media platforms, achieving an average annual growth of 470%, significantly enhancing brand awareness and engagement.
- Collaborated with engineering and sales teams to deliver high-impact large format artwork, marketing materials, and social media strategies for multiple annual tradeshows in the USA and EMEA, demonstrating strong project management and stakeholder communication skills.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

IZABELLE HAMMON

JULY 2017 - NOVEMBER 2017 (37)

Created visually distinguished design/marketing materials for events, e-commerce and quarterly product releases.

- Conceptualised and created new product range collateral working closely with directors, design managers, and social media coordinators to meet demanding release schedules.
- Increased efficiency of imaging team by directing photoshoots of products and packaging to generate templates that were simple to manipulate in postproduction.
- Delivered a physical/digital product guide for external stakeholders for the first time

PHOTOGRAPHER & MARKETING COORDINATOR

HARRIET KELSALL BESPOKE JEWELLERY MARCH 2014 - JULY 2017 (37.5)

Innovated at a senior level of the marketing team producing all imagery and design work to transition to an online-focused retail experience.

- Executed a full rebrand of the business collaborating with external design and web-development agencies to overhaul the look and feel of the brand.
- Created efficient image production pipeline to deliver 'magazine-worthy' studio and lifestyle imagery of all previous bespoke commissions in a fast-paced environment.
- Conceptualised, pitched and delivered quarterly digital and print campaigns that aligned customer age with national average engagement age.

BRAND AMBASSADOR

TED BAKER

JUNE 2012 - MARCH 2014 (40)

Delivered a customer-first luxury retail experience with a focus on personalised service, product knowledge, and maintaining high visual merchandising standards.

- Acquired in-depth knowledge of new product releases during head office training events and leveraged this knowledge to design and deliver internal staff training sessions, aligning product understanding with customer needs and brand values.
- Completed an intensive internal customer interaction training program, which
 equipped me with the skills to provide exceptional customer service to both new
 and returning customers.
- Contributed to achieving sprint and stretch sales targets by upholding high visual merchandising standards, proactively informing customers about ongoing promotions, and adhering to security policies to ensure inventory accuracy.